oh.. oh .. hey... how is it going?
Guess I should be teaching you something since this is an expert show, right?
Well, beer pong, beer pong.
Right, let me tell you the supplies needed in beer pong.
To start out you need beer, so we got it right here and you know what, no true expert beer pong player doesn't have his very own kegirator at hand.
So, I got my draft beer.
Let me show you the other supplies that we need, alright?
Okay, so we got our beer, alright?
Now we are going to need our four cups of beer.
Each team gets two cups of beer.
Then we are going to need two water cups, alright?
After the water cups, we are going to need two ping-pong balls.
The reason for the water cups is that we are going to have to clean off these ping-pong balls throughout the game because these are going to be going all over the table, they are going to be going into beer, they are going to be going all over the ground and stuff.
The water is actually to clean off the beer pong balls, okay?
Then each team has ten cups, okay?
Now these ten cups, you are going to need to fill with beer.
So, you got your beer, you got your cups, you got your water cups, you got your ping-pong balls, now all you need is something to play on.
What I have here is a professional style ping-pong table, alright?
Now, what I have done here is made an expert beer pong table.
This is up to expert qualifications in building a beer pong table.
Now in the world series of beer pong, they play with a lot smaller tables, but in my house we play with this big monster one.
It makes it a little bit harder and a little more competitive and the fun thing about this is that you can build your own beer pong table and have people sign all over it so it is always fun to look back and read what people have written and how many times you have one.
We have got tally's of everything, so, these are the supplies you are going to need, so maybe another supply would be a marker for your beer pong table.
Those are the supplies that you need, so let's move on to the next step.